simpopdf.com 2018-12-28

# Simpo Technologies Privacy Policy

Simpo Technologies ("Simpo Tech." or "We") are committed to protecting your privacy, so we develop this Policy for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. We aim to provide you with the world’s strongest security and privacy tools. Security and privacy matter to us, we know how important they are to you and we work hard to get them right. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you.

Our Commitment to your privacy

This privacy policy covers the Site and is applicable worldwide. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Simpo Tech. employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the whole company.

Information we collect

The types of information we collect and handle normally comprises:

i. Identity and contact details such as name, email address, phone number, credit card information, and mailing address  
ii. Product and service preferences  
Normally, we collect your personal information from you but on occasions we may obtain information about you from others. We may collect additional information about your company to provide better service for volume orders. We only collect information which is necessary for the purposes of your dealings with us. We do not collect information about anyone's political or religious beliefs, ethnic background, criminal history or sexual preferences.

Purpose of collection & use of personal information

The purpose for which we collect this information is to assist us in providing you with the products and services you have requested. We will not use your personal information for any purpose which is not related to the products or services you have requested or for any purpose which you would not reasonably expect us to use the information. We typically use your information for the following purposes: 

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

Customer Information and Credit Card Transactions

Simpo Tech. uses secure server hosted by SWREG and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

Cookies

We use cookies to collect aggregate data for statistical analysis. we automatically log certain non-personally identifiable information about visits to our website. This information is used for providing usage statistics, for instance we are interested in who links to us and which of our pages our visitors like to spend time on. 

Linking to other websites from our site

We have links to reputable websites on some of our pages in order to provide options to our visitors. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. When leaving our site to view one of these websites, we encourage you to review their privacy policies as we cannot guarantee the privacy of users while visiting other sites.

Anti-Malware Statement

Simpo Tech. STRONGLY OPPPOSES all forms of malware. Simpo Tech. applications will never intentionally jeopardize our customers' privacy or security. All applications are designed to be easily removable from the computer through an uninstall utility. Simpo Tech. does not employ the use of reinstallers and avoids all features that may be found in any type of malware. No Simpo Tech. application is designed to collect any personally identifiable information from any user. Simpo Tech. applications do not contain, nor are they bundled with, any third party applications (spyware, adware, malware, etc.) that would jeopardize our customers' security or their privacy. All Simpo Tech. applications pass both Kaspersky and Rising vigorous anti-virus/malware tests before public release.

Policy Changes

Occasional changes may be made to our privacy policy. Visitors are encouraged to check this page periodically to stay informed of current privacy guidelines. Acceptance of Terms: by using our website, you signify your acceptance of this website privacy policy. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated March 6, 2010.
